const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ὧδε',
    answers: ['hier'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐκεῖ',
    answers: ['daar'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ὅπου',
    answers: ['waar', 'waar vandaan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐγγύς',
    answers: ['nabij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'νῦν',
    answers: ['nu', 'op dit ogenblik'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'νυνί',
    answers: ['nu', 'op dit ogenblik'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἤδη',
    answers: ['nu', 'reeds', 'al'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἄρτι',
    answers: ['nu', 'zoeven', 'zoëven'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τότε',
    answers: ['dan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'παντοτε',
    answers: ['altijd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πάλιν',
    answers: ['weer', 'nog eens'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἔτι',
    answers: ['nog'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'οὐκέτι',
    answers: ['niet meer'],
    explanation: '(+ indicatief)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'μηκέτι',
    answers: ['niet meer'],
    explanation: '(+ andere wijzen)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'εὐθύς',
    answers: ['recht', 'meteen', 'aanstonds'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'εὐθέως',
    answers: ['meteen', 'aanstonds'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'σήμερον',
    answers: ['vandaag'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πῶς',
    answers: ['hoe'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ποῦ',
    answers: ['waar'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson37Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson37-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 37 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson37Vocabulary
